<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Day 24 RecyclerView</string>
    <string name="news_content">
        For the first time in decades, all three members of the Nehru-Gandhi family — Sonia, Rahul, and Priyanka — are now officially members of Parliament. Priyanka Gandhi, accompanied by her mother Sonia Gandhi, was joined by her brother, Rahul Gandhi, the Leader of Opposition, and her husband, Robert Vadra, for the special occasion.
Priyanka Gandhi’s victory in the Wayanad Lok Sabha bypoll, held alongside the Maharashtra and Jharkhand Assembly elections in 2024, has propelled her into Parliament with a remarkable win. She secured the seat with an impressive margin of 410,931 votes. This bypoll was necessitated after Rahul Gandhi vacated the Wayanad seat in favour of retaining his family bastion in Rae Bareli, following his double victory in the April 2024 general elections.
    </string>

    <string name="news_content2">
         Eknath Shinde On Meeting Amit Shah Amid Maharashtra Suspense
Eknath Shinde and Devendra Fadnavis met Amit Shah in Delhi
New Delhi: Maharashtra Chief Minister Eknath Shinde on Friday said he had "good and positive" discussions with Union Home Minister Amit Shah and BJP chief J P Nadda on the issue of government formation in the state. Speaking to reporters here before leaving for Mumbai, Mr Shinde said the decision on the next chief minister of Maharashtra will be taken "in a day or two" in another meeting of the Mahayuti coalition in the state capital.
Mr Shinde, along with Deputy Chief Ministers Devendra Fadnavis and Ajit Pawar, met Mr Shah and Mr Nadda late Thursday to thrash out a power-sharing pact for the next government in Maharashtra after the BJP-led coalition registered a thumping majority in the Assembly elections.
"We will take a decision (on Maharashtra CM) in a day or two. We have held discussions, and the discussions will continue. You will get to know when we take a final decision," the outgoing chief minister said.
    </string>

    <string name="news_content3">
        Mexican President Claudia Sheinbaum said on Wednesday Mexico would retaliate if U.S. President-elect Donald Trump followed through with his proposed 25% across-the-board tariff, a move her government warned could kill 400,000 U.S. jobs and drive up prices for U.S. consumers.
“If there are U.S. tariffs, Mexico would also raise tariffs,” Sheinbaum said during a press conference, in her clearest statement yet that the country was preparing possible retaliatory trade measures against its top trade partner.
Mexican Economy Minister Marcelo Ebrard, speaking alongside Sheinbaum, called for more regional cooperation and integration instead of a war of retaliatory import taxes.
    </string>
    
    <string name="news_content4">
        Actor Tabu is a legend in the Indian film industry, but she has also made waves internationally. Her latest Hollywood project is the big-budget HBO show Dune: Prophecy, in which she plays the character Sister Francesca. The show premiered a week ago to mostly positive reviews, but the premiere episode didn’t feature Tabu. The actor has now revealed when her fans can expect to see her.
Taking to Instagram, Tabu shared a new look as Sister Francesca and also revealed that the episode featuring her will stream on 16th December in India. The caption on her post read, “Prepare for a new Sister to show her strength. The Dune Prophecy episode featuring Tabu premieres December 16 in India.” Dune: Prophecy has been streaming on the JioCinema service in India.
    </string>
    
    <string name="news_content5">
        After selling equity for Rs 113,858 crore through exchanges in October, FPIs sold another Rs 41,872 crore of equity through exchanges till November 22, taking the total outflows to a whopping Rs 155,730 crore since October 1 this year, according to exchange data. “We don’t think FPIs are coming back in droves. The market might see fresh allocation in January after December year-end and vacation,” said an analyst.
FPIs invested Rs 9,947 crore on November 25 and Rs 1,157 crore on November 26. “There could be more selling by FPIs as they face year-end redemption from their investors,” he said.
    </string>

    <string name="news_content6">
        The Chief Executive Member (CEM) of Assam’s Karbi Anglong Autonomous Council (KAAC) claimed on Tuesday that “around 1,000” members of the Kuki community moved to the region from Manipur because of the ongoing violence in the state. However, local Kuki leaders from Karbi Anglong have said the claims are baseless.
The KAAC has jurisdiction over the two hill districts of Karbi Anglong and West Karbi Anglong, and governs them under provisions of the Sixth Schedule of the Constitution. This is a largely tribal region, with a mix of different tribes, of which the Karbis – Assam’s third largest tribe and its largest hill tribe – are the largest in number. Kukis and Hmars, who are also part of the Kuki-Zomi umbrella, are among the tribes in this region.
On Tuesday, KAAC CEM Tuliram Ronghang told reporters that he called a meeting with Karbi and Kuki leaders on November 28 to arrange to move out the Kuki people who he said had settled in the area after coming from Manipur.
    </string>
</resources>